newsbox.com 2013-03-28

# Newsbox

## Privacy Policy

Maintaining user privacy is essential to our service. We work hard to maintain a secure environment and adhere to rigorous principles to protect your privacy.

We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will never share your contact information with another user, without your consent. Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology. Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Newsbox Utility after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Newsbox.
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom the information may be shared.
  * How you can access and change your Account information.
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Newsbox.
  * Contact us by email to support@newsbox.com.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Newsbox by email at support@newsbox.com.

## Information Collection

### Registration:

In order to become a Newsbox user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief user overview, and choose a password.

### Profile Information:

Once a user, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your company, business initiatives, and business objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself andfind new opportunities in the Newsbox system.

## Information about your Contacts

In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Newsbox, you will enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by Newsbox to send your invitation including an invitation message. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to manually enter additional contact information in your account. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Newsbox network without your permission.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

### Cookies & Log Files:

Like most websites, Newsbox uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Newsbox to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Newsbox account. The next time you visit the Newsbox web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number) however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Newsbox site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Newsbox site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Newsbox web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Newsbox. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Newsbox Utility. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

### Advertisements:

We may, in the future, decide to post advertisements on select areas of the Newsbox utility. The advertisements would be in addition to standard featured listing options and may be services by third parties. The advertising technology providers use special technology to determine which advertisements will display in certain areas. We will not release your personally identifiable information to any advertising technology provider.

As we evaluate advertising opportunities, we will keep all efforts within the guidelines of this privacy agreement and other user agreements and customer agreements provided by us. In the event that we make an exception to deliver advertising to specific areas of our site that may be controversial or, in some case, potentially unwanted, we will provide opt-out opportunities.

### Children:

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

## Information Use

Newsbox is an online service dedicated to helping all types of businesses more effectively connect with target audiences. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to users of Newsbox. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by American Digital Networks, LLC, (ADN Media) from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Newsbox. This information can be utilized by Newsbox in such manner as Newsbox, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

### Newsbox Communications:

Newsbox will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of up to five welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Newsbox related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. Newsbox may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to customer_service@Newsbox.com.

### Customized Content:

Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network.

## Information Sharing

### Sharing Information with Third Parties:

Newsbox takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users activities on the site, please email customer service.

### Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services:

Newsbox partners with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from Newsbox to the partner if you choose to use the combined service.

### Communications Between Users:

Many emails you initiate through Newsbox, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Other communications that you initiate through the Newsbox website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

### Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

## Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Newsbox account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Newsbox website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Newsbox website. If you close your Newsbox account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Newsbox Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Newsbox Utility, please send your request to customer_service@Newsbox.com. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Newsbox under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to customer_service@Newsbox.com within three business days of our receiving it.

## Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Newsbox is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as credit card information) is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and our website. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Newsbox may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

## Questions or Comments

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@newsbox.com or contact us at:

Connectus Software  
Attn: Privacy Policy Issues  
PO Box 6607  
Annapolis, Maryland 21401
